hey everybody welcome to this a one
English listening practice video you can
use this video to practice your
listening and comprehension as I speak
before we start remember to subscribe to
the channel click on the bell and follow
us on Instagram you ready so today I'm
gonna talk about homes this is an
important topic because we talk about
our homes a lot let's talk about the
different types of homes some people
live in the houses some people live in
apartments and other people live in
other types of homes houses and
apartments are the most common types of
homes in big cities people often live in
apartments apartments are very common in
big cities they're usually smaller and
cheaper than houses some apartments are
in really tall buildings these buildings
can have 20 or 30 floors sometimes I
don't want to live on the 30th floor I
prefer living on the 1st or 2nd floor if
you live outside the city you probably
live in a house not an apartment people
that live in the countryside usually
live in houses these houses are usually
bigger than apartments they also have
backyards a backyard is the place behind
your house where you can have grass
trees gardens or a pool when I was a kid
I loved playing in my backyard it was
fun to play outside everyday most
apartments don't have backyards
they usually have balconies instead ok
now let's talk about the price of houses
and apartments in the u.s. houses and
apartments can be really expensive
if you live in a big city in my home
state of California houses and
apartments cost a lot of money the
average price of a house in California
is all six hundred thousand dollars
crazy huh it's also really expensive to
rent an apartment in California in the
US people usually rent apartments but in
some other countries people often buy
apartments when I was younger I shared
an apartment with other roommates it's
common to have roommates in the u.s.
sometimes you have good roommates and
sometimes you have bad roommates have
you ever had roommates before okay now
let's talk about other types of homes
some people live in condos which are
similar to apartments single condos are
part of a bigger building or complex
just like apartments but in the u.s.
many people buy condos but they don't
buy a partner one more type of home that
exists in the u.s. is the townhouse
townhouses are similar to normal houses
but they're often smaller and cheaper
also they're usually part of a community
of townhouses so there are several
different types of homes that people can
buy or rent some people prefer houses
some people prefer apartments and other
people prefer condos or townhouses I
think I prefer houses I hope I can buy a
house in the future all right that's all
for today leave a comment and tell me
what type of home you live in and
remember to subscribe to the channel
click on the bell and follow us on
Instagram
for more English tips and lessons I'll
see you next time
[Music]
[Applause]